As Ginni Bazlinton reached Antarctica, she found herself greeted by a group of little Gentoo penguins longing to say hello.
金妮·巴兹林顿抵达南极洲时，迎接她的是一群急着跟她打招呼的小巴布亚企鹅。
These gentle, lovely gatekeepers welcomed her and kick-started what was to be a trip Ginni would never forget.
这些温顺可爱的“守门人”迎接了她，也由此开启了一段注定让金妮终生难忘的旅程。
Ever since her childhood, Ginni, now 71, has had a deep love for travel.
金妮如今71岁，从童年起就一直深爱旅行。
Throughout her career as a professional dancer, she toured in the UK, but always longed to explore further.
在整个职业舞蹈演员生涯中，她一直在英国各地巡演，但始终渴望去更远的地方探索。
When she retired from dancing and her sons eventually flew the nest, she decided it was time to take the plunge.
等她告别舞台、儿子们也终于离家独立后，她认定是时候勇敢迈出这一步了。
After taking a degree at Chichester University in Related Arts, Ginni began to travel the world, eventually getting work teaching English in Japan and Chile.
在奇切斯特大学获得相关艺术专业学位后，金妮开始周游世界，后来在日本和智利找到了教英语的工作。
And it was in Chile she discovered she could get last-minute cheap deals on ships going to Antarctica from the islands off Tierra del Fuego, the southernmost tip of South America.
也正是在智利，她发现，从南美洲最南端火地岛附近的岛屿开往南极洲的船，临近开船时能买到便宜的特价票。
“I just decided I wanted to go,” she says.
“我就是打定主意要去，”她说。
“I had no idea about what I’d find there and I wasn’t nervous, I just wanted to do it.
“我完全不知道会在那里看到什么，也不紧张，我就是想去做这件事。
And I wanted to do it alone as I always prefer it that way.”
而且我想独自去，因为我一向更喜欢那样。”
In March 2008, Ginni boarded a ship with 48 passengers she’d never met before, to begin the journey towards Antarctica.
2008年3月，金妮和48位素不相识的乘客一起登上一艘船，开始了前往南极洲的旅程。
“From seeing the wildlife to witnessing sunrises, the whole experience was amazing.
“从观赏野生动物到亲眼看日出，整个经历都太棒了。
Antarctica left an impression on me that no other place has,” Ginni says.
南极洲给我留下的印象，是别的任何地方都不曾给过我的，”金妮说。
“I remember the first time I saw a humpback whale; it just rose out of the water like some prehistoric creature and I thought it was smiling at us.
“我记得第一次看到座头鲸的情景；它就那样从水里浮了上来，像某种史前生物，我觉得它在对我们微笑。
You could still hear the operatic sounds it was making underwater.”
你还能听到它在水下发出的歌剧般的声音。”
The realization that this is a precious land, to be respected by humans, was one of the biggest things that hit home to Ginni.
意识到这是一片珍贵的土地，应当受到人类的尊重——这是让金妮感触最深的事情之一。